The Reverend Al Sharpton criticized pro-Palestinian demonstrators who disrupted
House Minority Leader Hakeem Jeffries during a speech at his National Action Network convention.
Take a listen to what was going down.
At one point, the crowd started chanting, no justice, no peace over the protesters.
So what a lot of people may not understand is that Hakeem Jeffries is bought and sold
by AIPAC, which is the American-Israel political action PAC, whatever, you know, like the lobbyist.
He has received over $300,000 in 2023 to 2024 alone in campaign funding from AIPAC.
This also was frustrating and disgusting to watch because I cannot stress to you all the
level of force that the security was removing these protesters out of the room with.
And I'm like, OK, this is supposed to be a black space.
The protesters were all black men.
Al Sharpton is literally just on stage, like watching it happen.
Then he comes back on the mic and calls the protesters rented Uncle Toms.
Here we have Al Sharpton, who has a black space that is clearly not keeping black people safe,
calling the black people protesting rented Uncle Toms.
You are literally being a rented Uncle Tom.
But I want to just address the idea of like what makes a black space a black space.
If you can't feel safe in a black space, then what are we even really doing?
Yeah.